God bless America... they're going to need it.
SLC Punk is a comedy, drama, crime film directed by James Merendino.
Two former geeks become 1980s punks, then party and go to
concerts while deciding what to do with their lives.
Stevo, played by Matthew Lillard.
Bob, played by Michael A. Goorjian.
Trish, played by Annabeth Gish.
Sandy, played by Jennifer Lien.
Dad, played by Christopher McDonald.
Sean, played by Devon Sawa.
is a 1998 American comedy-drama film written and directed by James Merendino.
The film centers around Steven "Stevo" Levy, a college graduate and
punk living in Salt Lake City during the mid-1980s.
was chosen as the opening-night feature at the 1999 Sundance Film Festival.
Merendino created the film based on his experience growing up in Salt Lake City.
Although the film is not autobiographical, Merendino has said
that many characters were based on people he knew.
The film explores themes of male friendship, punk rock, breaking
the fourth wall, redneck, salt lake city, utah.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.